

ASHLEY W O H L R A B

BUSINESS STUDENT

CONTACT

845 405 1219 ASHLEY.WOHLRAB1@MARIST.EDU ASHLEYW706.GITHUB.IO

PROFILE

Currently a junior at Marist College, studying Business Administration, Human Resources, and Data Science and Analytics. Relevant experience in the field of HR as well as experience in fast food and customer service. Truly passionate about helping others and making the world a better place for all.

EXPERIENCE

HUMAN RESOURCES INTERN

ANDERSON CENTER FOR AUTISM | JAN 2019 - MAY 2019

- Served as an assistant in various departments of HR including Employment, Benefits, and Recruitment.
- Learned about each department's role in the hiring process.
- Learned about the day-to-day functions of a non-profit organization.

CREW TRAINER

MODENA TRAVEL PLAZA | JUN 2015 - JAN 2019

- Maintained high standards of customer service during highvolume, fast-paced operations
- Cross-trained and coordinated scheduling with team members to ensure seamless service
- Communicated clearly and positively with coworkers and management

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, MAJOR IN BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

MARIST COLLEGE | 2016 - 2020

SKILLS

- Microsoft Office Suite
- Event Planning
- Strong Leadership and delegation skills
- Excellent time management
- Experience with Python, HTML, and CSS.
- Organization Skills
- Excellent Customer Service Skillset
- Willingness to Learn new skills
- Loyal, Devoted, and Driven to Succeed

NOTABLE AFFILIATIONS

SOCIETY OF HUMAN RESOURCES MANAGEMENT MEMBER OF MARIST COLLEGE CHAPTER OCT 2018 - PRESENT

NATIONAL SOCIETY FOR LEADERSHIP AND SUCCESS MEMBER OF MARIST COLLEGE CHAPTER APR 2017 - PRESENT